

I am a UX engineer with 10+ years of design experience and 3+ years of development experience, specializing in building scalable front-end products with great user experiences. I am looking for a hybrid UX designer / developer position to support between design and development.

CONTACT

Phone +1 (469) 386-6307

Email develop.jay8675@gmail.com

Address Dallas, Texas

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/jay8675

PORTFOLIO

Website jaykim-dev.netlify.app

Github github.com/jaehyung8675

Graphic https://bit.ly/3HuOFU6

SKILLS

Programming JavaScript

React Next.js Node.js Express.js Sass / SCSS HTML5 CSS

Design User Experience (UX)

User Interface (UI)

Product Web Visual Graphic

Tools Git

Github

Visual Studio Code

Figma Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer / Part-timeJuly 2017 - PresentBinnerri Presbyterian ChurchRichardson, Texas

- Create all visual designs for over 400+ members to engage them in worship and events.
- Revamp 2+ websites to make them more visually and experientially accessible to customers using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.
- Create presentations for speakers to support their sermons and easily interact with the audience.
- Complete projects on time and deliver them to clients according to the church's schedule and goals.

UX EngineerJanuary 2020 - January 2023OTA World LLCCarrollton, Texas

- Led a design team to create and enhance all visual design, and maintained company websites.
- Designed and developed product pages using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, and used by over 100+ merchants (Costco, Amazon, Sam's Club, Home Depot, etc.) to market their sites.
- Managed projects using Agile to quickly deliver products to stakeholders, vendors, and customers.
- Created global CSS to enforce a consistent style across all Shopify e-commerce sites.

Graphic Designer

January 2014 – December 2014 Dallas, Texas

Ravis's Ware House

- Created print materials such as brochures and flyers to promote products that helped increase sales.
- Implemented lighting and design in a studio environment to produce product images.

Product Designer / Internship

January 2010 – January 2011 Seoul, South Korea

Pantech Wireless, Inc.

- Completed 2 major projects with all mobile design processes from concept to building mock-ups.
- Explored interactions and design ideas by creating storyboards, user flows, and prototypes.
- Collaborated with team members to implement new concept designs during the summer in Japan.

Unemployed 2012 - 2013 / 2015 - 2019

Pursued to finish my education degrees, and had 5 short-term jobs as a freelance designer.

EDUCATION

University of North Texas2020 – 2022M.A. in Interaction DesignDenton, TexasSouthern Methodist University2017 – 2019B.F.A. in Art & Graphic DesignDallas, Texas

Brookhaven CollegeA.A. in General Studies

2014 – 2017

Farmers Branch, Texas

Christian For The Nations InstituteAccredited Theological Degree

Dallas, Texas

Hongik University2006 – 2010

B.A. in Product Design

Sejong, South Korea